

NAHNA ABDUL WAHAB

CONTACT

- 7027858757
- nahnaabdulwahab@gmail.co m
- Las Vegas, NV 89119

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A passionate student of computer science with an orientation towards both software & hardware solutions. I believe understanding the human to computer interface and how software & hardware are used in industry is what will dictate a successful organization from those that will be added to the history books of failed organizations. I have worked in sales and as a computer science student, the blend is perfect for a career in a telecommunication company

SKILLS

- Problem Solving Ability
- Proficiency in Microsoft Office
- Leadership & Mentoring
- Coding
- Sales
- Analytical Skills
- Problem Identification & Technological Solutions.
- Creativity
- Critical Thinking

EXPERIENCE

CERTIFIED NURSING ASSISTANT Mar 2020 - 2020

Visiting Nurse of Westchester, White Plains, New York

I worked as a Certified Nursing Assistant to provide care to the elderly during the peak of COVID19 after my other job was shut down. My duties as a caregiver involved giving compassionate care to my client by taking them to their appointments, doctor's visits, ensuring they take their medications, providing companionship etc.

IT TECHNICAL SUPPORT REPRESENTATIVE & INSURANCE AGENT

Aug 2018 - Mar 2020

Prudential Insurance Company, White Plains, New York

- Sales Sold insurance policies
- Installing and configuring new technology rolled out by company.
- Troubleshooting Issues with office computers.
- Maintenance & documentation of data network systems and sending reports to superiors.
- Maintenance to existing hardware and computer systems.
- During down time, I performed the functions of an insurance agent to assist my area manager.

SAMSUNG & NEST BRAND ADVOCATE/TRAINER & SALES LEAD

Feb 2014 - Jul 2018

Microcenter, Yonkers, New York

I started as a <u>salesperson</u> at Microcenter and grew to become the brand advocate & trainer for Samsung and Nest, I was one of the few people who got hands on training on new products (both hardware & software) before they are release onto the market. This allowed me to train all product technicians and sales team on the functionalities and specifications of all new Samsung and Nest products sold by Microcenter.

EDUCATION

ASSOCIATE OF SCIENCE - COMPUTER SCIENCE

Graduate September 2021

Borough of Manhattan Community College, New York, New York I was a member of the STEM team of my school.

Courses I have taken include but not limited to Python, C++, JavaScript, HTML, HDL etc.

COMMUNITY SERVICE

JCY Westchester Partners., Yonkers, NY

Mentoring:

- Assisted children to develop their reading skills.
- Listen and inspire kids to learn and work hard.

Sacred Heart, Mount Vernon, NY Soup Kitchen

- Assisted & participated in the preparation of meal for the needy
- Provided support services (counseling/aid) for the needy

LICENSE & CERTIFICATIONS

TECHNICAL SUPPORT FUNDAMENTALS COURSERA | GOOGLE

• Credential ID JYUENRLD2JVP

Credential URL

https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/JYUE NRLD2JVP

REFERENCES

Stella Bartels Visiting Nurse of Westchester 914-523-2377

Saeed Adewole Prudential Insurance Company 347-484-3818

Charlene Brown Manager - Microcenter 914-471-3752